<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<!-- Use either "\n" or XML whitespace return to make linebreaks; both method works -->

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<modNameReadable>Elite Bionics Framework</modNameReadable>
		<linkUrl>https://github.com/Vectorial1024/EliteBionicsFramework</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v1_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Thank you for using Elite Bionics Framework, a framework to enable hediffs to modify body part max HP.|- Added "linear adjustment" parameter for EBF Hediffs; refer to documentation on how they work, and how body part max HP are calculated</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v1_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Added "scaling adjustment" parameter for EBF Hediffs; refer to documentation on how they work, and how body part max HP are calculated</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Updated mod for RimWorld v1.1.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_1_0_B01</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Beta 1.|
- Framework addition: now possible to adjust melee attack damage for Hediffs and Hediff_Implants; refer to GitHub documentation for more info.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_1_0_B02</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Beta 2.|
- Fixed unexpected, critical "failed to apply Harmony patches" bug due to RimWorld update v1.1.2598</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_1_0_B03</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Beta 3.|
- Fixed a NullReferenceException related to social fights.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_1_0_B04</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Beta 4.|
- Technical update: Max-HP-related transpilers now at priority = Priority.First .</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v3_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.0.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Updated to RimWorld v1.2.|
- Notice to C# modders: a new C# class EBFEndpoints is available to read the max HP of body parts under the effects of EBF; more details at the GitHub repo</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Standardize entire mod to use namespace "EBF" to reduce confusion.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed potential tool-related null-reference error with Save Our Ships 2
- Improved tool comparison logic to reduce occurence of null-reference errors with various other bionic mods (please see if those errors are fixed!)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Attack Power Adjustors now skips some problematic hediffs when checking applicability; should result in even less NullReferenceException</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Recalibrated this mod to be compatible with RW v1.3
- Pre-RW v1.3 compatibility is not affected; this is making use of the multi-version feature of RW</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed Harmony patching conflicts with Pawnmorpher (not backported)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.5.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Traded some features:
- [+] This mod no longer gives exception when used with Humanoid Alien Races; but
- [-] EBF hediffs that increases pawn core part HP now does NOT reduce % chance of pawn getting stunned after taking blunt damage
+-------------</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.6.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Improved the previous trade:
- [+] This mod no longer gives exception when used with Humanoid Alien Races; and
- [+] EBF hediffs that increases pawn core part HP now CAN reduce % chance of pawn getting stunned after taking blunt damage (cancels the negative effects of v4.0.5)
- [*] Now must be loaded before Humanoid Alien Races; PLEASE USE THE AUTO-SORT TO REAPPLY LOAD ORDER!
+-------------|Special thanks to GitHub user RocketDelivery for this fix!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_7</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.7.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Merry Christmas!|
- Added compatibility with EdB Prepare Carefully: you can now see correct body part max HP calculated by EBF without errors
- Added compatibility with CM Callouts: you can now see correct motes (based on body part max HP) when a body part is destroyed
- Added compatibility with Moody: you can now see correct body part max HP calculated by EBF without errors</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.8.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Not much going on.|
- Fixed max HP modification display formatting
- Fixed verb power modification showing as max HP modification
- Improved accuracy of detecting EdB Prepare Carefully: hopefully there are less false positives that leads to patching errors</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_9</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.9.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Housekeeping, and some deeper thoughts.|
- Fixed error wth Pawnmorpher; fundamentally, both mods tried to modify the same thing at the same time
- Notice: EBF has detected a rare 3-mod conflict: using EBF + Pawnmorpher + CompactHediff together is discouraged until we figure out what is going on, and meanwhile if you only use at most 2 of them from that combo, you won't see any problems
- Notice: EBF has noticed more and more 3rd party mods creating custom HP-increasing bionics without using EBF, which may cause confusion, incompatibilities, and incorrectness; EBF is currently thinking of a solution to this</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Hi all! Elite Bionics Framework v5.0.|
It has been about 4 years since the initial conception of Elite Bionics, and Elite Bionics Framework has grown so much. Thank you all for the continued support!|
For a long time, I noticed that there are several mods out there that provides HP-increasing effects by themselves. I generally leave them be, but some of them are causing incompatibilities with EBF and with each other, which is problematic.|
This is why I have decided to evolve EBF a bit more by letting it be a unifying bridge between the various mods that provide body part HP modification. I call this Community Unification.|
Note that this mod only allows them to work with each other together; the individual effects are not modified in any way. You will still be seeing effects and numbers of the individual mods themselves.|
And of course, disclaimers: I am not affiliated with any of the mod authors out there. I do not claim ownership on any of the mods out there. All I do is simply to ensure that all mods can run smoothly alongside each other.|
- The Community Unification: a decision has been made to unify the many mods out there that modify body part max HP but may potentially conflict with each other
- To XML modders depending on EBF: no update is needed
- The inner code of EBF has been changed somewhat; C# modders be aware (even though I believe there aren't too many breaking changes)
- I am unaffiliated to any of the mods below
- I claim no ownerships of any of the mods below|
- The following mods are unified:
  - Quality Bionics
  - CONN
  - Cyber Fauna
  - Pawnmorpher
  - GeneticRim/Vanilla Genetics Expanded
  - Level This
- If QualityBionics is installed: fixed the wrong implementation of QualityBionics causing HP modification to double-count for eg arms and legs
- If Pawnmorpher is installed: we standardized the patches with Pawnmorpher, so that we also show additional UI text dedicated to Pawnmorpher
- Also fixed error with Pawnmorpher regarding "error setting up text" when reading body part summary|
- Added some tips to the in-game tips library
- No update needed for Compact Hediffs, unless they would like to readjust their UI using the latest EBF functions and methods
</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>@everyone|
Please check that you are using the correct version of Cyber Fauna, thanks!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- The following mods are unified:
  - Mechalit Core|
@everyone|
Please check that you are using the correct version of Mechalit Core, thanks!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed unreasonale version-check error messages for MechalitCore and CyberFauna users</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed extreme lag in the Form Caravan screen introduced in v5.0.0</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.5.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed TargetParameterCountException while trying to read Pawnmorpher HP (fix was shipped in v5.0.4 as a random test but I was not aware of its effectiveness before this moment)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.6.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed body part max HP wrongly persisting over different pawns (error introduced in v5.0.4; the lag fix from v5.0.4 is still here)
- (Version unknown) Pawnmorpher no longer gives harmless "Pawnmorpher violates the EBF Protocol" error message; protocol-checking is disabled for Pawnmorpher for compatibility reasons</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_7</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.7.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- The following mods are unified:
  - Half dragons (v1.3 ver; mod ID Monti.HalfDragons, Steam ID 2556121262)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_7_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.7.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>No new features, only an amendment to the v5.0.7 news: I wrote something wrong, so I intend to withdraw it and write it again.
- Added compatibility with Half Dragons (v1.3 ver; mod ID Monti.HalfDragons, Steam ID 2556121262)
- Half Dragons is NOT unified in any way! (tbh their mod does not boost body part HP, so there is nothing to unify)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Partially updated to RW v1.4; please see explanation below:|
Seeing how a lot of extra features got added to this mod during RW v1.3, I will do the RW v1.4 update by stages:|
- Stage 0: wait for Ludeon to release RW v1.4 (done)
- Stage 1: wait for UnlimitedHugs to release HugsLib for v1.4 (done)
&gt; Stage 2: release EBF for v1.4 (&lt;--- we are here)
- Stage 3: wait for others to release their mod updates for v1.4
- Stage 4: reconfirm compatibility with related 3rd party mods|
This will take a while. If you don't use too many related 3rd party mods, then perhaps this update is already sufficient; but if you are relying on the Community Unification features, I would suggest putting this on hold for a while until I complete rechecking everything.|
Or, alternatively, you could go ahead and see if this update works with the related 3rd-party mods, saving me some time for rechecking.|
This is something I came up with for RW 1.4/BioTech, which touches bionics. Perhaps this is the procedures going forward if any more (relevant) RimWorld update is released in the future.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Removed $HugsLibChecker from this mod because it is obsolete and is causing problems.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Updated compatibility with Cybernetic Organism and Neural Network (CONN).|
A number of other mods were reviewed, and they were either not yet updated to match RW v1.4, or they worked fine with this version of EBF.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Fixed unexpected inompatibiity with Yayo's Animations (failed to patch [...]: invalid IL code) by moving one of EBF's patches even earlier in the execution order.
Please use auto-sort to put this mod above Yayo's Animations!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>A few things:|
- Confirmed compatibility with Prepare Carefully [1.4]
- Confirmed compatibility with Pawnmorpher [1.4]
- Fixed "nullable object must have a value" error when e.g. the game checks for social fights for pawns having EBF-provided verb power adjustment (special credits to Evono for finding this out during an unrelated auto-test!)
- Compatibility with Callouts [1.4] delayed due to unexpected owner change on Callouts's side
- Compatibility with Save Our Ships 2 [1.4] pending</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Experimental: mods with no loaded contents (hopefully this means unloaded mods) are no longer detected by this mod for Community Unification; should reduce confusing error messages</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.6</assemblyVersion>
		<content>I have noticed that CONN has officially chosen the Elite Bionics Framework to provide HP-buffing effects. Welcome CONN! And thank you for choosing the EBF.|
- Removed CONN from the Community Unification scheme (note: CONN is now a regular EBF mod instead)
- Using CONN will no longer throw red errors on game startup</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_7</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.7</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Removed CONN-related code from the DLL; maybe this fixes the performance drop?</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.8</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Optimized performance drop when looking at the Health tab on pawns (side effect: max HP display text may update slightly later after installing/changing EBF bionics)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>A big update to Elite Bionics Framework in recent months.|
- Added Multiplayer compatibility
- Greatly optimized performance by using a better caching system; no more lag spikes! (in fact, no more lag in general...)
- Thus, removed the "delayed update" side effects introduced in v5.0.8.8
- Optimized detection of Pawnmorpher in calculating body part max HP
- Fixed wrong detection of active mods in determining cross-mod unification (completes the feature in v5.0.8.5)
- Confirmed compatibility with Callouts 1.4 (by Profligate)
- Re-added missing loading screen tips (whoops...)|
Note: Multiplayer compatibility was tested on a local-self-to-self setup. Hopefully, it indicates general Multiplayer compatibility.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Improved compatibility with RimThreaded</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- "Compatibility with RimThreaded" no longer impacts performance too much (problem introduced in v5.1.1)
- Optimized performance (should see less slowdowns when pawns are healing)|
Note: you will probably see some lag shortly after starting/loading a game, but the lag will reduce over time, and that is normal; when a game is started/loaded, EBF is probably busy calculating the max HP values for all the newly-loaded pawns.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_3_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Technical update:
- EBF.GetMaxHealthWithEBF will now return the cached max HP values by default|
Explanation/Examples:
- Generally reduced lag when things happen, such as:
- Reduced lag when looking at the health tabs of untended bleeding pawns
- Improved performance when looking at the health tab via Compact Hediff|
Other changes:
- Further optimized the caching; stuttering should be generally less frequent
- Improved detection of Pawnmorpher hediff changes|
Still, remember: EBF will need time to warm up when the game loads new pawns, but after a while, EBF will just run in the background smoothly.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_3_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.3.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Small bugfix with detection of incompatible mods.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_4_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Further optimized performance: will self-cleanup when pawns/corpses are destroyed
- Fixed actually-broken Half Dragons compatibility|
The performance improvements in this update will be helpful when, e.g., you are running a chicken farm and are now butchering the chickens, or when you are cleaning up after defending against a large raid.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_5_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.5.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Finally fixed "not really working with Mechalit Core" (oops!)
- Added compatibility with Vanilla Psycasts Expanded (special thanks to GitHub user delmain)
- Changed some of the hand-crafted transpilers to CodeMatcher transpilers (also special thanks to GitHub user delmain)|Now, go forth and spread the gospel of CodeMatcher transpilers.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_6_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.6.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Finally fixed "max HP does not update after installing a new bionic" (oops!)
- Added compatibility with Immortals
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_7_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.7.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>After much delays, I am back with an update, unfortunately not for RimWorld 1.4.|- Compatibility with RimWorld 1.5
- Compatibility with other mods will be checked one by one, as they are updated
- Technical: max HP after EBF is now rounded up to the nearest integer, just the same as vanilla calculations, so no more e.g. "42.6" max HP
- Mod version is now provided in About.xml; this is v5.1.7.0 of the mod
- Technical: reduced mod size by removing the PDB files
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_7_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.7.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>And here is the cumulative bugfix update.|- Added compatibility with Pawn Quick Info
- Fixed broken compatibility with Moody (overdue; special credits to GitHub user dougbenham)
- Technical: converted the rest of the transpilers to use CodeMatcher; the patches should be much more future-proof after this|Eventually, this mod should become a low-maintenance mod.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_7_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.7.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Another cumulative bugfix update.|- Fixed broken compatibility with Pawnmorpher (overdue; special credits to GitHub user quicksilverfox)
- Fixed broken compatibility with EdB Prepare Carefully|Special Announcement:
Support for Mechalit Core and Cyber Fauna may be dropped in the future depending on the situation, just as DaLLaN intended. Previous (RW 1.4-) versions will not be affected.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_7_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.7.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Removed compatibility with Pawn Quick Info (note: compatibility is now provided by them, so the feature is actually "moved" to their side).</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_8_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.8.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>An update.|- Now requires another mod Visible Error Logs; this is required so the crowd-sourced compatibility checking can continue effectively
- Fixed compatibility with Prepare Carefully
- Negotiating compatibility with Save Our Ship 2 (new feature under discussion) (yes SOS2 is back!)
- Negotiating compatibility with Quality Bionics (Continued) (existing feature under discussion)
- Removed compatibility with Half Dragons (mod is discontinued); previous versions not affected by this change|Hopefully, in the coming days, we will know how to deal with Quality Bionics (Continued).</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_8_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.8.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Negotiations with Quality Bionics (Continued) has concluded.|- Adjusted compatibility with Quality Bionics to not trigger with Quality Bionics (Continued)
- Added compatibility with Quality Bionics (Continued)
- Clarified mod requirements with Visible Error Logs in About.xml|Summary of what happened: in a confusing move, Quality Bionics (Continued) renamed some of their code, resulting in unexpected patch failures. This is very different from previous continuations where nothing was renamed or changed, so it counts as a new mod rather than an update of an old mod.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_8_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.8.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Completely removed declared dependency on Visible Error Logs (VEL).

In a confusing move, I have wrongly believed that error logs would appear even if dev-mode was off. It was never the case. Therefore, VEL was actually an unrelated "new feature", and there is/was no justification to suddenly require VEL to begin with.

The mistake was to push VEL when it was unnecessary. I deeply appologize for that.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_2_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>A rather large update to Elite Bionics Framework in recent months. The rarely-used tool-power-adjust module has been rewritten entirely, and after around 3 years inside the beta purgatory, it is now finally properly released.

- Tool power calculation is now consistent with the mod docs
- Whole-body hediffs now apply their tool power adjustment to all of the pawn's tools instead of throwing an exception (e.g.: infernal heart from Beliar Xenotype)
- Fixed "tool upgrade power adjustment" not actually replacing the original tool
- Tool power linear adjustment may now be a float instead of int
- Optimized calculation of tool power adjustment (read: should reduce lag with e.g. shoulder turret from LTS Integrated Implants)

This opens up some interesting ideas for other modders:

- Animal bionics that scales up the animal's original attack power
- Bionic knuckles that slightly boosts a pawn's attack power
- Abilities that applies a temporary hediff to buff a pawn's melee attack power
- etc etc</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_2_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.2.0.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Retargetted ProthesisHealth (i.e., Mechalit Core and Cyber Fauna) to use Mlie's community service version for RW 1.5.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_2_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.2.0.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Added compatibility with BetterPawnInfo.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_3_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.3.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Early season's greetings!

- Fixed inconsistency with tool power calculation (basically, general bionic implants vs AddedPart bionics); previously, this may result in unintended OP bionics
- Added clarification tooltip on tool power adjustment effects
- Added compatibility with Save Our Ships 2
- Added compatibility with Altered Carbon 2

With this, our RimWorld 1.5 update is complete.
</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_3_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.3.0.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>HotFix: fixed Altered Carbon compatibility not working.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_3_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.3.0.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>HotFix2: fixed Altered Carbon compatibility not working. (I'm eyeballing it)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_3_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.3.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Another season, another update for Elite Bionics Framework.

- [BioTech] Fixed Xenotype-related body part max HP problems
- Finally fixed Altered Carbon patching problems by using an alternative approach</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_4_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>This mod is now updated for RimWorld 1.6, with no code/feature changes. As usual, we will be semi-regularly rechecking for supported mod updates in the coming days/weeks/months.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v6_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>6.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>A technical but milestone update.

!!! IMPORTANT !!!

- Decoupled from HugsLib; depends on Harmony instead
  - You should manually review the mod options!
  - We still recommend you use HugsLib to send bug reports
  - For these update news, your choice: they will go away if you disable/uninstall HugsLib
- Added new way for C# modders to manage compatibility with EBF; see the GitHub README for more details
  - The plan is to let Quality Bionics Remastered adopt this method of compatibility, to reduce the mess on both sides
- Removed support for Cyber Fauna and Mechalit Core since they have unstable governance
  - Previous builds for RW 1.5 are unaffected by this change

EBF has become very mature and stable over the past 6 years. With this update, I can safely fade to the background to continue observing the modding community.

Thank you all for continuing to use this mod!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v6_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>6.0.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>A minor technical update.

- Removed support for Fluffy's Mod Manager since vanilla replacement &amp; ecosystem already exists (o7)
  - That Manifest.xml file was never updated for years anyway
- Removed compatibility with Quality Bionics and Quality Bionics (Continued)
  - Previous builds for RW 1.5 are unaffected by this change
- Note: compatibility with Quality Bionics Remastered is handled via the new compatibility pathway introduced in 6.0.0
  - QBR has some backwards compatibility for QBC and 1.5 EBF

This concludes the compatibility migration for Quality Bionics Remastered: instead of this Framework patching QBR to achieve compatibility, QBR now actively provides the intended value to the Framework.
Things should be much easier for everyone involved going forward.
</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v6_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>6.0.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>A minor technical update.

- Adjusted support for Callouts (Continued)
  - Compatibility now handled on their side
  - Previous builds for RW 1.5- are patched to not detect Mlie's variant
</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v6_0_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>6.0.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>A bugfix update.

- Fixed legacy EBF compatibility for Callouts (Continued) not triggering
- Fixed legacy EBF 1.5 compatibility with Quality Bionics Remastered
</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v6_0_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>6.0.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Fixed EBF Legacy error when Quality Bionics Remastered is not loaded. (ooof!)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v6_0_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>6.0.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Fixed EBF Legacy error spam when Quality Bionics Remastered is loaded. (ooof!)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>