<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<!-- Use either "\n" or XML whitespace return to make linebreaks; both method works -->

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<modNameReadable>Elite Bionics Framework</modNameReadable>
		<linkUrl>https://github.com/Vectorial1024/EliteBionicsFramework</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v1_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Thank you for using Elite Bionics Framework, a framework to enable hediffs to modify body part max HP.|- Added "linear adjustment" parameter for EBF Hediffs; refer to documentation on how they work, and how body part max HP are calculated</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v1_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Added "scaling adjustment" parameter for EBF Hediffs; refer to documentation on how they work, and how body part max HP are calculated</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Updated mod for RimWorld v1.1.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_1_0_B01</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Beta 1.|
- Framework addition: now possible to adjust melee attack damage for Hediffs and Hediff_Implants; refer to GitHub documentation for more info.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_1_0_B02</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Beta 2.|
- Fixed unexpected, critical "failed to apply Harmony patches" bug due to RimWorld update v1.1.2598</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_1_0_B03</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Beta 3.|
- Fixed a NullReferenceException related to social fights.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v2_1_0_B04</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Beta 4.|
- Technical update: Max-HP-related transpilers now at priority = Priority.First .</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v3_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.0.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Updated to RimWorld v1.2.|
- Notice to C# modders: a new C# class EBFEndpoints is available to read the max HP of body parts under the effects of EBF; more details at the GitHub repo</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Standardize entire mod to use namespace "EBF" to reduce confusion.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed potential tool-related null-reference error with Save Our Ships 2
- Improved tool comparison logic to reduce occurence of null-reference errors with various other bionic mods (please see if those errors are fixed!)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Attack Power Adjustors now skips some problematic hediffs when checking applicability; should result in even less NullReferenceException</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Recalibrated this mod to be compatible with RW v1.3
- Pre-RW v1.3 compatibility is not affected; this is making use of the multi-version feature of RW</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed Harmony patching conflicts with Pawnmorpher (not backported)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.5.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Traded some features:
- [+] This mod no longer gives exception when used with Humanoid Alien Races; but
- [-] EBF hediffs that increases pawn core part HP now does NOT reduce % chance of pawn getting stunned after taking blunt damage
+-------------</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.6.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Improved the previous trade:
- [+] This mod no longer gives exception when used with Humanoid Alien Races; and
- [+] EBF hediffs that increases pawn core part HP now CAN reduce % chance of pawn getting stunned after taking blunt damage (cancels the negative effects of v4.0.5)
- [*] Now must be loaded before Humanoid Alien Races; PLEASE USE THE AUTO-SORT TO REAPPLY LOAD ORDER!
+-------------|Special thanks to GitHub user RocketDelivery for this fix!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_7</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.7.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Merry Christmas!|
- Added compatibility with EdB Prepare Carefully: you can now see correct body part max HP calculated by EBF without errors
- Added compatibility with CM Callouts: you can now see correct motes (based on body part max HP) when a body part is destroyed
- Added compatibility with Moody: you can now see correct body part max HP calculated by EBF without errors</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.8.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Not much going on.|
- Fixed max HP modification display formatting
- Fixed verb power modification showing as max HP modification
- Improved accuracy of detecting EdB Prepare Carefully: hopefully there are less false positives that leads to patching errors</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v4_0_9</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.9.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Housekeeping, and some deeper thoughts.|
- Fixed error wth Pawnmorpher; fundamentally, both mods tried to modify the same thing at the same time
- Notice: EBF has detected a rare 3-mod conflict: using EBF + Pawnmorpher + CompactHediff together is discouraged until we figure out what is going on, and meanwhile if you only use at most 2 of them from that combo, you won't see any problems
- Notice: EBF has noticed more and more 3rd party mods creating custom HP-increasing bionics without using EBF, which may cause confusion, incompatibilities, and incorrectness; EBF is currently thinking of a solution to this</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Hi all! Elite Bionics Framework v5.0.|
It has been about 4 years since the initial conception of Elite Bionics, and Elite Bionics Framework has grown so much. Thank you all for the continued support!|
For a long time, I noticed that there are several mods out there that provides HP-increasing effects by themselves. I generally leave them be, but some of them are causing incompatibilities with EBF and with each other, which is problematic.|
This is why I have decided to evolve EBF a bit more by letting it be a unifying bridge between the various mods that provide body part HP modification. I call this Community Unification.|
Note that this mod only allows them to work with each other together; the individual effects are not modified in any way. You will still be seeing effects and numbers of the individual mods themselves.|
And of course, disclaimers: I am not affiliated with any of the mod authors out there. I do not claim ownership on any of the mods out there. All I do is simply to ensure that all mods can run smoothly alongside each other.|
- The Community Unification: a decision has been made to unify the many mods out there that modify body part max HP but may potentially conflict with each other
- To XML modders depending on EBF: no update is needed
- The inner code of EBF has been changed somewhat; C# modders be aware (even though I believe there aren't too many breaking changes)
- I am unaffiliated to any of the mods below
- I claim no ownerships of any of the mods below|
- The following mods are unified:
  - Quality Bionics
  - CONN
  - Cyber Fauna
  - Pawnmorpher
  - GeneticRim/Vanilla Genetics Expanded
  - Level This
- If QualityBionics is installed: fixed the wrong implementation of QualityBionics causing HP modification to double-count for eg arms and legs
- If Pawnmorpher is installed: we standardized the patches with Pawnmorpher, so that we also show additional UI text dedicated to Pawnmorpher
- Also fixed error with Pawnmorpher regarding "error setting up text" when reading body part summary|
- Added some tips to the in-game tips library
- No update needed for Compact Hediffs, unless they would like to readjust their UI using the latest EBF functions and methods
</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>@everyone|
Please check that you are using the correct version of Cyber Fauna, thanks!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- The following mods are unified:
  - Mechalit Core|
@everyone|
Please check that you are using the correct version of Mechalit Core, thanks!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.3.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed unreasonale version-check error messages for MechalitCore and CyberFauna users</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed extreme lag in the Form Caravan screen introduced in v5.0.0</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.5.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed TargetParameterCountException while trying to read Pawnmorpher HP (fix was shipped in v5.0.4 as a random test but I was not aware of its effectiveness before this moment)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.6.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Fixed body part max HP wrongly persisting over different pawns (error introduced in v5.0.4; the lag fix from v5.0.4 is still here)
- (Version unknown) Pawnmorpher no longer gives harmless "Pawnmorpher violates the EBF Protocol" error message; protocol-checking is disabled for Pawnmorpher for compatibility reasons</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_7</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.7.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- The following mods are unified:
  - Half dragons (v1.3 ver; mod ID Monti.HalfDragons, Steam ID 2556121262)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_7_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.7.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>No new features, only an amendment to the v5.0.7 news: I wrote something wrong, so I intend to withdraw it and write it again.
- Added compatibility with Half Dragons (v1.3 ver; mod ID Monti.HalfDragons, Steam ID 2556121262)
- Half Dragons is NOT unified in any way! (tbh their mod does not boost body part HP, so there is nothing to unify)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Partially updated to RW v1.4; please see explanation below:|
Seeing how a lot of extra features got added to this mod during RW v1.3, I will do the RW v1.4 update by stages:|
- Stage 0: wait for Ludeon to release RW v1.4 (done)
- Stage 1: wait for UnlimitedHugs to release HugsLib for v1.4 (done)
&gt; Stage 2: release EBF for v1.4 (&lt;--- we are here)
- Stage 3: wait for others to release their mod updates for v1.4
- Stage 4: reconfirm compatibility with related 3rd party mods|
This will take a while. If you don't use too many related 3rd party mods, then perhaps this update is already sufficient; but if you are relying on the Community Unification features, I would suggest putting this on hold for a while until I complete rechecking everything.|
Or, alternatively, you could go ahead and see if this update works with the related 3rd-party mods, saving me some time for rechecking.|
This is something I came up with for RW 1.4/BioTech, which touches bionics. Perhaps this is the procedures going forward if any more (relevant) RimWorld update is released in the future.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_1</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.1</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Removed $HugsLibChecker from this mod because it is obsolete and is causing problems.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_2</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.2</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Updated compatibility with Cybernetic Organism and Neural Network (CONN).|
A number of other mods were reviewed, and they were either not yet updated to match RW v1.4, or they worked fine with this version of EBF.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Fixed unexpected inompatibiity with Yayo's Animations (failed to patch [...]: invalid IL code) by moving one of EBF's patches even earlier in the execution order.
Please use auto-sort to put this mod above Yayo's Animations!</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_4</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.4</assemblyVersion>
		<content>A few things:|
- Confirmed compatibility with Prepare Carefully [1.4]
- Confirmed compatibility with Pawnmorpher [1.4]
- Fixed "nullable object must have a value" error when e.g. the game checks for social fights for pawns having EBF-provided verb power adjustment (special credits to Evono for finding this out during an unrelated auto-test!)
- Compatibility with Callouts [1.4] delayed due to unexpected owner change on Callouts's side
- Compatibility with Save Our Ships 2 [1.4] pending</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Experimental: mods with no loaded contents (hopefully this means unloaded mods) are no longer detected by this mod for Community Unification; should reduce confusing error messages</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_6</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.6</assemblyVersion>
		<content>I have noticed that CONN has officially chosen the Elite Bionics Framework to provide HP-buffing effects. Welcome CONN! And thank you for choosing the EBF.|
- Removed CONN from the Community Unification scheme (note: CONN is now a regular EBF mod instead)
- Using CONN will no longer throw red errors on game startup</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_7</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.7</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Removed CONN-related code from the DLL; maybe this fixes the performance drop?</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_0_8_8</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.8.8</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Optimized performance drop when looking at the Health tab on pawns (side effect: max HP display text may update slightly later after installing/changing EBF bionics)</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>A big update to Elite Bionics Framework in recent months.|
- Added Multiplayer compatibility
- Greatly optimized performance by using a better caching system; no more lag spikes! (in fact, no more lag in general...)
- Thus, removed the "delayed update" side effects introduced in v5.0.8.8
- Optimized detection of Pawnmorpher in calculating body part max HP
- Fixed wrong detection of active mods in determining cross-mod unification (completes the feature in v5.0.8.5)
- Confirmed compatibility with Callouts 1.4 (by Profligate)
- Re-added missing loading screen tips (whoops...)|
Note: Multiplayer compatibility was tested on a local-self-to-self setup. Hopefully, it indicates general Multiplayer compatibility.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- Improved compatibility with RimThreaded</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_V1024_EBFramework">
		<defName>EBF_v5_1_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.1.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>- "Compatibility with RimThreaded" no longer impacts performance too much (problem introduced in v5.1.1)
- Optimized performance (should see less slowdowns when pawns are healing)|
Note: you will probably see some lag shortly after starting/loading a game, but the lag will reduce over time, and that is normal; when a game is started/loaded, EBF is probably busy calculating the max HP values for all the newly-loaded pawns.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

    <!--
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>Desync_1_2_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.2.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>First paragraph.|img:Things/Item/Meal/Fine,Things/Item/Meal/Lavish,Things/Item/Meal/Simple|caption:This is a caption.|Another paragraph with &lt;b&gt;rich text&lt;/b&gt;.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
    -->
</Defs>